Hello friends, my name is Jai Sharma and
welcome to our
YouTube2 plan. Friends, this plan has
just been launched by the company and the company has
created such a hype that in this plan the
company is going to give you a lot of things,
unlimited will give you short time,
unlimited will give you restoration,
you can choose unlimited claim once in your life, so the
company is promoting a lot of things
in this, a lot of things have been
given by the company in this plan, so
friends, today we will talk about this plan, so
friends, before moving ahead,
subscribe to our channel because you will keep getting
notifications of such videos that we bring for you, so
let's start
[Music]
Friends, this company has a cashless network of
more than 99500, it has
tie-ups with more than 9500 hospitals all over
India, wherever you go, you will get this almost everywhere.
Talking about the claim settlement ratio,
it is around 95 to 98, it
varies in different years,
if we talk about the cashless approval time  So the
company takes two hours, if
all your documents are complete then it will take
two hours from there. If we
talk about the claim settlement type, then here
you get an in-house claim. If we talk about tax benefits, then the
premium that you pay
in this company, whether you are paying for yourself
or for your mother-father or for
your parents,
if your age or that of your parents is 60
years or less than 60 years, then
you will get a benefit of Rs. 000 for you, Rs. 10000 for your
mother-father and if the age of your mother-father is
above 60 years, then you will get a benefit of Rs.
50,000. If you are also above 60 years, then
you will also get a benefit of Rs. 50,000.
If you are less than 60 then Rs. 25,000,
if you are above 60 then Rs. 50,000. If we talk about free loop,
then it is for 15 days. If
you understand some things after taking the policy  If the policy does
not come or you feel that you have been
sold a policy by telling you wrong things, then
you can cancel this policy within 15 days
and you get 100% refund of your money.
Talking about grace period, you
get a grace period of 30 days here.
After the policy expires, you have 30 days time.
After the policy expires,
you can renew the policy within 30 days and you continue to get
all the benefits of the policy.
Talking about policy cancellation, cancellation is available. You
can cancel the policy whenever you want throughout the year,
but the company will cancel the policy on a
pro rata basis as per the validity of your policy
and will
deduct your premium from you there.
You will not get the full premium. You will get the full premium
only on free look. If you
cancel the policy within 15 days, then you will
get your full premium back, but if you
do it after that, then some money will be deducted from it.
Talking about portability,
portability is available here.  If we
talk about the policy tenure available, then you get three tenures
here, you can take the policy for one year,
for 2 years or for 3 years together
and in this tenure,
whenever you take a policy for 2 years,
you get a discount of 10% and
whenever you take a policy for 3 years,
you get a discount of 15% on the total premium. The company
offers you here early renewal discount.
If we talk about early renewal discount, if your
policy is about to expire and
you renew that policy one month before its expiry,
then the company
gives you extra benefit there also and
gives you a discount of % on renewal.
If you renew on time,
when your policy is about to expire,
then you will not get this renewal discount,
but if you do it in advance, 45
days before or 30 days before, then you will get an
extra discount of 2% there.
Friends, let's talk about premium discount,
friends, the company has divided the area into zones,
zone A, B, C, D, which  Whichever zone you
come in, the premium is charged from you according to that zone. The
premium is high in zone A
and the premium will be the lowest in zone D. So,
whichever zone you come in, the
company will charge you premium according to that zone.
Talking about roll over sum shot, where you
port the policy, then
you will get a minimum sum shot of 10 lakhs. If you are
taking the policy fresh, then you
can take a policy of 5 lakhs, but if you are porting, then
you can port with a minimum of 10 lakhs,
you will not be able to port below that.
Talking about family floater limit,
friends, what people consider a family is
2 or 3,
you will not be able to add more members than that, so you will be able to add two
adults and three children, maximum five people
in the policy
and if we talk about dependent child, then
you can add dependent child from 91 days to 30 years in your policy.
As soon as the child crosses 30 years and
turns 31, he will be automatically removed from your policy
and he will be added in a new policy.  The policy
company will make and give it to you there. Now friends, let's move
ahead and talk about what
you get in this plan. So
friends, first of all let's talk about the entry age.
Whenever you take a policy, what should be your entry age? The
minimum age is 18 years
and there is no maximum limit because no
one is going to live till 125 years in today's date,
so there is no limit for the maximum.
Your age should be minimum 18 years.
You can purchase the policy.
Talking about sum assured, the
company is offering you a minimum sum assured of Rs 5 lakh. After that,
you can choose the option of Rs 75 lakh, 10 lakh, 15 lakh, 20 lakh, 25 lakh, 50 lakh,
1 crore, 3 crore and unlimited sum assured
here.
As you increase the sum assured,
your premium will also keep increasing there.
Talking about in-patient care,
if you are admitted in a hospital, then
in in-patient care, you will get up to a sum assured of whatever
your sum assured is.  It will pay the
entire amount. Talking about day care, there
is no limit there too. The
company is going to pay you up to the sum there.
Talking about modern treatment which includes
robotics, the company is going to pay you
up to the sum there too.
Talking about post-hospitalization, whenever you are
admitted for any disease, all the
expenses incurred 90 days before that, the
company is going to pay you up to the sum there.
Talking about post-hospitalization, the
company will cover your expenses for up to 180 days after discharge
and will cover up to the sum there.
Talking about AYUSH treatment, friends,
AYUSH treatment is also covered here, in which all
your Unani, Siddha, Homeopathic,
Ayurvedic treatments are included, the
company also covers you up to the sum here.
If we talk about domestic road ambulance, there is no
limit here.
Whatever the expenses, the company is going to pay you 100% here.
Talking about donor expenses,
if a donor donates an organ or donates something to you,
then
there  But the company is going to bear the expenses of both you and the donor
and will pay you up to the sum shot there.
If there is a domicile hospitalization and
you are not able to go to the hospital and
your treatment will be done at home, then the
company is going to pay you up to the sum shot
there too. Friends, let's talk about
bonus, then the company gives you a guaranteed bonus here,
that too 20% of the sum
shot. You get a guaranteed bonus every year and
if you take a claim, it does not decrease either, so it
means you are going to get guaranteed,
whatever has increased once, it will not decrease again.
Talking about reset benefit,
friends, you get unlimited reset benefit,
when whatever time shot you take, if that
time shot gets over, then
your time shot gets reset again
and you get the entire sum shot there again,
but at one time you can
claim only that much sum shot as
you have bought.
After discharge, if you get
admitted again, then you will have to claim the entire sum shot again.  You will be
able to use the summer shade, but the
maximum summer shade you can use at one time is the amount
you have covered. If you have
taken a cover of Rs 10 lakh, then the maximum
you will be able to use in one claim is only Rs 10 lakh.
If you are admitted again after discharge, the
company will reset the
cover and give you the cover. So the maximum claim in one go will be Rs
10 lakh only. Yes, if a
bonus of Rs 20
or any other bonus has been added there, you will be
able to use it once in the first claim,
but whenever your first sum is exhausted with the second claim,
you will be able to use your reset sum only
when you are admitted again for any disease.
Talking about bariatric surgery,
there too the company is covering you up to the sum covered.
Whatever your expenses are, the
company will cover the entire in-patient
treatment for the surrogate mother. So, for the surrogate mother
also, you will pay up to Rs 5 lakh here,
but this is only
for complications.  If the
surrogate mother faces any complication at the time of delivery or otherwise, then the
company gives you a cover of ₹1 lakh for that complication.
In-patient treatment for Ukai
donor: If a woman, a Ukai donor,
helps another woman in surrogacy
and donates an egg, then in that condition
also the company will cover her and if there are any
complications, then the company will pay up
to 5 lakhs there too. Now let's talk about
waiting period. If we talk about initial waiting period,
whenever you take a policy, for the
first 30 days the company does not cover anything
except an accident. If there is
any problem due to an accident, then the
company will cover it, otherwise the company will not cover it.
After 30 days, your cover will start
and there you will start getting different waiting periods,
like talk about PD,
if you have any disease at the time of taking the policy,
any pre-existing disease you are suffering from
and you tell the company
about that disease, then
you  A 36-month waiting period has to be served there.
If there is any disease and the company
accepts your policy and
accepts your proposal, then
you may have to take out a 36-month waiting period.
Talking about specific diseases, there are some diseases
which are slow-growing and
grow slowly in your body. The
company covers such diseases after 24 months. It will
not cover you initially; for that,
you will have to wait a minimum of 24 months.
Talking about critical illness, the company
is covering critical illness after 90 days, which is a very good thing.
Many companies cover it in 90 days.
If we talk about the waiting period for bariatric surgery,
there is a
waiting period of 24 months. Where the
company is covering bariatric surgery, it
is covering up to some extent.
There, you also have to wait for 2 years.  But you will have to take out this
thing which is bariatric surgery,
not every company covers it, but in this plan the
company is covering it for you. If we talk about the
waiting period for hypertension, diabetes, cardiac, then
here the company imposes a waiting period of 90 days.
After 90 days of taking the policy,
all these things are
covered for you. Talking about the waiting period for maternity, the
company also provides you maternity in this plan.
If you take maternity cover,
you add maternity as an add-on in
this policy, then you have to
take out a waiting period of 24 months there.
Now friends, whatever things we have seen till now,
whatever waiting period we have seen till now, whatever
benefits we have seen till now, all those
benefits are inbuilt in this plan.
Whenever you purchase this plan,
you will purchase its base plan without any add-
on. So all these things which I have
told you till now, you are going to get all these things,
but now I am going to
tell you some things which you should include
in your policy.  You can add on, which
can enhance the benefits of your policy.
You can reduce your premium with some things. So, the
company gives you all these add-ons here
and in the name of add-ons, the company is
not giving just a few add-ons, it is giving you a lot of
add-ons here, so you can
change many things in this, so let's
see what all you can do in it.
First of all, let's talk about
Infinite Care, so friends, unlimited
coverage for one claim, this is such a benefit
which you have not got in any insurance policy till date. The
company tells you
that whenever you add this add-on,
after adding it, the company gives you an option once in your life
that no matter how big the
cover is, suppose you have taken a sum shot of ₹0 lakh,
but your expense in any claim is ₹
50 lakh, ₹80 lakh, then the company
says that if you add this add-on, if
you add this add-on, then
we will pay you a big sum shot once in your life
if you ever need it, but
that is only for us.  You will pay there only once
and this sum, this cover, we have to take it
within 2 years of taking the policy,
if you do the third renewal
then you will not be able to take this cover and
you will not be able to take its benefit, let's talk about number two
Power Booster, so friends,
100% bonus per year, friends, the bonus that you
get here is inbuilt, you get it
at 20, but if you
add this add-on in the name of Power Booster, then
you start getting it 100% and there
your up to 100% was increasing, that means 10 lakhs
is short, by doing it at 20, in 5 years
it will increase by 100%, so your sum will become 20 instead of 10,
but there is no limit here, it will increase by 100%
every year, the 20 that is increasing will definitely increase,
along with this it will increase by 100%
and there is no limit on it, it will become
1 crore in 10 years, if you are
taking a policy of 10 lakhs, you will get 50 lakhs  If you take a policy of Rs. 10 crore,
it will become Rs. 5 crore in 10 years, Rs.
10 crore in 20 years and
it will reach Rs. 15 crore in 30 years. So, the
company is offering you this thing in this plan
that whether you claim or not, you will keep getting
it every year and it will always keep
increasing for you, it will never decrease here. The
third option of their add-on is Jump
Start. Friends, asthma, diabetes,
hypertension, hyperlipidemia,
obesity and
PTC are covered for you in 90 days,
but if you add this add-on Jump Start,
then as soon as your 30 days are over,
all these diseases are covered here.
For this, the company will charge you a little
extra premium and will
cover all the diseases there. Now let's talk about
maternity at number four. Friends,
maternity is also available in this plan,
but it is a bit costly. We tried adding it,
but it is a bit costly. If it suits you, then
you can take it. Now, here's
how much cover will you provide here. The company will provide cover up
to Rs. 10 per sum of Rs. 10  Off sum share
means if you have a sum share of 5 lakhs then
you will get 500000. If your
sum share is 10 lakhs then the maximum you will get is 1 lakh. The
maximum limit in this is 50000, 75000
and 1 lakh. You will not get anything above 1 lakh.
Whether you take a plan of 20 lakhs or 20 lakhs, you take a plan of 25 lakhs or
50 lakhs then you will get the
maximum. You will get a minimum of 50000. For 5 lakhs,
you will get 75000 and 10 lakhs. Along with adding this plan,
you can also add this.
If you add in the new born baby cover, then
the sum of maternity, whatever will be
your sum of maternity as per your plan,
suppose it is 75000, then here
you will get double for the new born baby,
but if your plan is 1 lakh then
you will get double there also, you will get 2 lakhs, you will get
new born baby cover.  Now let's talk about baby cover.
Vaccination for new born baby,
which is done in the first year, the
company also pays you for that here.
You will have to add this add-on also.
You can do 1% off sum whichever is shot,
but the maximum you will get here is 0000 to 10000
only.
For the vaccination of the child in the first year,
now our fifth add-on is B Fit.
Friends, you will have to add all these add-ons.
None of these are inbuilt in this. All these
add-ons will have to be added for that, for that you will have to pay a
separate premium here.
Talking about B Fit, B Fit has
OPD cover here, you can take their OPD. There are
many plans in OPD also, so
as soon as you choose a plan,
you will get plans there in OPD.
Whatever your plan suits, you
can take it there. Accordingly, your
premium will be added there.
Talking about claim protector, friends, there are
many non-medical charges in your policy
which the companies do not pay for,
but  If you add claim protector here, then the
company also pays you the non-medical charges here.
Talking about inflation protector,
friends, as inflation keeps increasing every year,
if you add this inflation
protector, then the company
also keeps increasing your sum shot according to inflation.
If we talk about domestic air ambulance, then friends, you can take up to sum shot
domestic air ambulance,
but for that you will have to
add this add-on and whatever
your cover will be, up to sum shot the company will
provide you air ambulance there.
Talking about conveyance benefit, up to
20000, the company pays you here whatever
such expenses whenever you are admitted in the hospital
and after being discharged you
recover but you cannot go to work, then the
financial company pays you a benefit up to
0000, so you
can add this benefit to it and
you can avail this benefit there, so the company
pays you up to 00 if
you  If you are recovering after being discharged and your
recovery is taking some
time, then the company
gives you a benefit of up to Rs. 00 there. Now friends, let's talk about
nursing at home.
Whenever you are discharged and
after that, if you keep a qualified nurse with you, then the
company pays you Rs. 2000
per day, but its maximum
limit is 10 days. For 10 days, the
company keeps you there for Rs. 000 per day. If we
talk about health checkup, then the company
gives you health cover of Rs. 0.5 per sum off
of total sums and maximum up to Rs. 5000. So maximum
you get Rs. 000. You
can get the test done for Rs. 000 or if you get some of their
listed tests done, then they will be done on
your cashless basis there.
If we talk about critical illness, then
critical illness is up to Rs. 50 lakh short
cover here, but the maximum limit there is Rs.
50 lakh if ​​your policy is ₹  If the insurance cover is of Rs. crore
or Rs. crore, then even there
you will get a maximum cover of Rs. lakh for critical illness
and for that you will have to
add a critical illness add-on here,
but there is one more limit here
that the maximum age of an adult should be
50 years. If you are 51
years old, then you will
not be able to avail the benefit of this critical illness benefit. This is
only for people up to 50 years. Let's talk about
personal accident, friends,
personal accident is also your cover here. If
you take this cover, then up to a sum shot, here
also the maximum limit is 50 lakhs. So
you can take a personal accident cover of Rs. 50 lakhs,
but the maximum age will be
65 years. Like here,
50 years is the limit for critical illness and 65 years for personal accident,
only people up to 65 years will be
able to avail it. If you are 66 years old,
then you will not be able to avail its benefit.
Talking about voluntary copay,
friends,
you can also avail some discount in the policy.
If you choose this option of
voluntary copay, then some of
your premium gets reduced there and at the time of claim,
whatever claim comes, it will be on a
sharing basis of 10, 20, 30, 40 or 50, this will be
your ratio, the rest the company will pay. If you do this, then the
company will pay 90%, if you
do this, then the company will pay 70%, 30%,
your premium will get reduced, this much
percentage will be your sharing,
so you will pay this copay, the rest will be done by the company.
Dependent Accommodation: So friends, whoever
stays with you in the hospital,
any one person who leaves his work and
stays with you in the hospital for two days, four
days, six days, then the company takes care of him too
and if you add this amount, then the
company will pay him Rs. 000 per day but the maximum
limit will be up to 10 days. The
company will pay him maximum for 10 days.  It
is durable medical equipment,
so friends, if you
want to buy durable medical equipment, then whenever
you add this add-on,
you will be able to buy it up to some limit, but the maximum
limit is 5 lakhs, so you will be
able to purchase equipment only up to 5 lakhs,
for that only the company will pay you there.
Talking about tele-consultation,
it is available for unlimited times, you can take
tele-consultation on video call or
audio call as many times in a year, there is no
limit on it. Talking about room
modification, it is available, you do
not get a suite room, you do not get a deluxe room,
you get a single private room in-
built in this policy, so if you want then
By adding this addon, you can enhance it and
decrease it. The number
one option will be Any Room
Category. So as soon as you upgrade it, the
option of Any Room Category will appear.
You can choose any room. You can
take a deluxe room or a suite room.
Your premium will increase there.
Twin Shared Room. If you decrease from a single private room
to a twin sharing room,
then your premium will reduce a little.
You
can take a twin sharing room instead of a single private room. The
third option is 1 per room and 2 per room
for ICU. The company also gives you the third option that
you charge for ROM. If
you take 1 per room and 2 per room
for IO, then the company reduces your premium a
little more, but this is
only for policies up to Rs 75 lakh.
If you take a sum above that, then
you will not be able to add this third addon.
Only the first or the second one will be
able to be added here. Now let's talk about it.
Whenever you take this policy,
what discounts can you avail in this policy?
So the first discount
is the wellness program. So friends, there is an
option of a wellness program in this policy.
If you attend that wellness program
and follow their terms and conditions, then
you can get a discount of up to 30% on the renal plan.
Credit score based discount. Friends,
if your credit score is good, if your
civil score is good, then you can also get this
discount through your PAN number.
But if your
civil score is bad, then keep this in
mind that your loading may also be levied here. So keep in
mind that you can avail this discount only if you have a good civil
score. So,
you should not avail this discount on a bad civil score. Let's
talk about the long term
discount. The long term discount is the same.
If you are taking a policy for two years, then
you will get a discount of 10%.
If you are taking a policy for nine years, then
you will get a discount of 15% on the entire premium
there. Early renal
discount. I have already told you that
2.5 You will get an early renewal discount
whenever you renew the policy 30 days in advance or
45 days in advance, then
you will get this discount there.
Network Advantage Friends, they have a network called
PPN Network which is called
Preferred Provider Network.
If you go to this network and get your treatment done, then
you get a discount of 10%
on your entire bill, but if it does not come under PPN
then you may have to pay a payment of 20% there. Let's
talk about voluntary
copayment discount, I
told you, whatever the copayment is on 10%, 20%, 30%,
you will have to pay it. You will have to add this add-on, only
after that you will be able to add it.
Now friends, let's move ahead and talk about
Infinite. Whenever you
go to the IIC website or
open the browser of this plan, then you will
see a lot of Infinite. The
first thing you will see is Infinite.
Infinite Sum Shot, Infinite Claim Amount,
Infinite No Claim Bonus.  Infinite Reset, the
company is promoting it as if it
means the company gives everything unlimited, so what does it
mean, so first of all let's talk about
Infinite Sum Shot, Infinite Sum Shot
means the company is offering you Sum
Shot Unlimited where you and the company offers
you a Sum Shot of 1 crore or 2 crore,
where the company is offering you the option of 1 crore, 3 crore
and then Unlimited Sum Shot, so if you
want in your policy, you
can also get Unlimited Sum Shot by paying extra premium,
now let's talk about Infinite Claim Amount,
friends, the company is giving such an option
in Add-on, this first option is your
inbuilt but the second option is
your Add-on, if you take this add-on
then once in your life the company
is ready to give you a big claim, that is your
policy is of 10 lakh or 20 lakh, but
if you add this add-on and your
claim sometimes comes to 80 lakh, 50 lakh or
₹ lakh  If it comes then the company is ready to
give you that claim once in your life
but you will get it only once.
If you take the claim once then that
option will expire for you and you will
not be able to take it again. So for that you will have to
add the infinite claim amount option which is an add-on here.
Infinite No Claim Bonus so friends you get No Claim Bonus
at 20% but whenever you
add it then you get it 100% and you will keep getting it for
unlimited time. If the policy runs for 10 years then
your 10 lakhs will become 1 crore.
If it is a policy of 50 lakhs then it will become 5 crores,
similarly it will become 10 crores. Then
it will keep increasing. There is no
limit to it. You will keep getting 100% sum assured every year.
After that let's talk about
infinite reset. Suppose the sum assured is 10 lakhs
then it will keep getting reset again and again in your policy. It will keep getting reset for
unlimited time
as many times as you want.
Your sum assured will get exhausted.
You will keep using this reset again and again and this
is also available on the same disease for
which you have already taken a claim,
you can use this reset amount for this claim in the same policy year, so
friends, these are the four things which the
company is promoting in the name of Infinite in its brochure and on its
website that it is an unlimited
thing, however, you will not get these things everywhere,
you will not get this sum assured option everywhere,
claim amount, no claim bonus,
you will not get these everywhere, there is a limit in these too,
but the company is
giving you unlimited here,
now friends, finally let's talk about support,
friends, their toll free number for support is
18266, if you have to file a claim, you have to get a
policy endorsed, you are facing any
other problem in the policy, then
you can talk on this number and you will get
all the solutions there, let's talk about email ID,
if you want to mail,
you do not have to call, you just have to email
or the matter is done  If you have to
send some documents to the company or send some
emails, then go there to
ihealthcare@icicilombard.com. If
you need any information about this policy,
its brochure, its forms,
any other information, then you
can visit the company's website
www.icc. You will get all the details there.
Whatever details you need,
you will get them all on our website.